Guide to the May Chen Papers WAG.301
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- East Coast Asian Student Union Conferences, National Conference on Women and the Law, Memorial Notebook for Professor Lee C. Lee, Po Ling Ng's School Board Election etc. 1960-2006, 1960s-2002; 452460 (Box 10)
  - Rising to the Challenge, Asian Student Unity Conference, Harvard University 1982, 487658 (Box 10)
  - Asian Americans and "the American Dream" East Coast Asian Student Union Conference, Brown University, March 16-March 17, 1984, 487659 (Box 10)
  - Various Asian American Organizations College Newsletters and Information 1982-1996, 487660 (Box 10)
  - Asia Conference 1983, 487661 (Box 10)
  - More college Asian American Organization flyers, syllabus for Asian American Experience course, letter from Asian American Legal Defense and Education Fund 1982, 487662 (Box 10)
  - Sixties Student Literature 1960-1970, 487663 (Box 10)
  - Where is Home? A Conference on the Past and Future of Chinese in the Americas, New York University, October 10-October 12, 1997, 487664 (Box 10)
  - Memorial Notebook for Professor Lee C. Lee 1988-2006, 487665 (Box 10)
  - Non-Govermental Organization Women's Conference in Beijing (2) 1995, 487666 (Box 10)
  - Booklets on Non-Governmental Organizations concerning Women 1995, 487667 (Box 10)
  - The Women's Bureau, Women Thinking Globally Acting Locally on the Road to Beijing and the 21st Century, New York, April 22, 1994, 487668 (Box 10)
  - Poll Coordinator, Frank Ling, 180 Mott Street, Little Italy Senior Center, 1996; 487669 (Box 10)
  - School Board Elections New York City 1996, 487670 (Box 10)
  - School Board Complaint 1996, 487671 (Box 10)
- Po Ling Ng's School Board Election Campaign Materials (1996), 1996-1998; 452534 (Box 11)
- Proclamation from the Office of the Mayor of New York declaring "Chinese Heritage and Culture Week" January 26, 1987; Mass Rally in Chinatown Poster August 28, 1998, 487338 (Box 12)
- NGO Forum on Women (Beijing), 1995 (Box 13, Folder 1-5)
- Labor Tour to Japan, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6-10, Box 14, Folder 1)
- University of Massachusetts-Amherst Labor Studies Materials, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 11-17)
- Union Anti-Sweatshop Materials, 1988-2010 (Box 14, Folder 2-17, Box 15, Folder 1-20)
- David Dinkins Campaign and Asian Community Materials, 1988-1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Asian Labor Materials, 1987, 2006-2011 (Box 15, Folder 22-25, Box 16, Folder 1-4)
- Chinese Labor Tours: Journals and Memorabilia, 2005-2011 (Box 15, Folder 5-9)
- Asian Pacific American Labor Alliance Organizing Materials, 2010-2011 (Box 16, Folder 10-17)
- Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Local 1199 Chinese Activist Training, 2004-2010 (Box 16, Folder 18-19, Box 17, Folder 1-3)
- Union of Needletrades, Industrial, and Textile Employees (UNITE) Immigrant Project, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 20-21)
- Health Care Research, 2006 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
- Garment Workers Union Files and Triangle Fire Anniversary, 1994, 2005-2008 (Box 17, Folder 6-19)
- Labor Rights Training Materials, 1988-2010 (Box 18, Folder 1-19)
- Photographs: Personal and Labor Tours, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 20-23)
- Collected Video Documentaries, 1988-1997 (Box 19, Video 1-6)
- Video recordings: Speeches, Conferences, and Demonstrations, 1990-2005 (Box 19, Video 7-23)
- Conference Badges, 1996-2000 (Box 20)
- Buttons, 1980s-2000s (Box 21)
- Labor Tours: Tote Bag and Gift Plate from Guangzhou Labor Union, undated (Box 22, Item 1-2)
- APALA Biennial Convention: Tote Bag, 2009 (Box 22, Item 3)
- Poster: Activist Bill of Rights, undated (Flat-file-folder 1)
- Poster: Tea and Justice (signed), 2007 (Box MSOS 008, Folder 1)
- Unprocessed Digital Records: Lunar New Year Celebration Photos, Slideshows, Reports, 2001-2012 (Box 23)